{
    "subject": "resource/Warner_Baxter",
    "predicate": "ontology/deathCause",
    "object": "resource/Pneumonia",
    "human_readable": "Warner Baxter died due to Pneumonia.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8094491958618164,
            "question": "How did Warner Baxter die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7714837789535522,
            "question": "What was the cause of Warner Baxter's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7573111057281494,
            "question": "Warner Baxter died from what medical condition?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6978489756584167,
            "question": "What was the medical reason behind Warner Baxter's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6580384969711304,
            "question": "Warner Baxter succumbed to which disease?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6054678559303284,
            "question": "Name the illness that caused Warner Baxter's death."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5575287938117981,
            "question": "Due to what did Warner Baxter pass away?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5219850540161133,
            "question": "Pneumonia resulted in the death of whom?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45494890213012695,
            "question": "What ailment ultimately took Warner Baxter's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4379527270793915,
            "question": "What illness led to Warner Baxter's passing?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Warner Baxter died due to Pneumonia.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7195_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What ailment ultimately took Warner Baxter's life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7195_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Pneumonia resulted in the death of whom?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7195_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Due to what did Warner Baxter pass away?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7195_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7195_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7195_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7195_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7195_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7195_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7195_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7195_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7195_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7195_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7195_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. The documents mention that Warner Baxter suffered from pneumonia and this hastened his death (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7195/re-ranker-msmarco/45.txt), which is consistent with him dying due to pneumonia."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents mention that Warner Baxter had a lobotomy for severe arthritis pain and later died of pneumonia. This supports the statement that Warner Baxter died due to pneumonia."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}